HameFura, I Reincarnated
into an
Otome Game
as a
Villainess
with only
destruction flags···
aimaina I my me datte guruguru mazetara
If you mix it round and round it becomes unclear
akogare no kyuu tenkai ni niau kamo ne
With an unexpected development, maybe it will look good
ren ai nara iza morase
If it's love, express it now
tobikiri no dessert
with wonderful desserts
amazuppai cho misu wa oyurushi asobase
An addictive sweet and sour mix, I'm sorry to have fun
mawaru uruwashiki koi moyou
Love is a spiral pattern that spins on and on
chotto souzou naname you he massugu susume
I need to stop and think before moving forward
otome no route wa hitotsu janai
A maiden's route is not just one!
hatto suru lucky na ima ni gokigen you
My heart feels surprisingly lucky now
itsudatte maemukina desu
And so I will remain optimistic
ai mo kawarazu ni touhonseisou kou kando wo agete
If you want to win the game of love, you have to risk it all
kiyoku tadashiku utsukushiku are to wa yoku itta monda na
It's a pure, intense and beautiful feeling, so fight for it
kitto warui happy na mirai ni gokigen you
I still don't know if my ending will be happy or not
itsu datte maemukina desu
But I will remain optimistic
Episode 7
I Entered a Dangerous Dungeon...
If I could be reborn,
I'd want to be her friend again.
Let's stop for tea on the way home.
Sure. Want to try the new place by the station?
That's a good idea!
Right?
I-I'm sorry!
Please don't die!
I can't bear the thought
that I killed someone with my butt!
Um, I'm fine...
I'm sorry!
H-Hey!
Oh, thank goodness! Are you hurt?
No, I'm fine.
I'm really, really sorry!
Don't worry about it.
What were you doing, anyway?
This tree was practically calling out to me.
I had to climb it.
But I got ahead of myself, and my foot slipped.
Wait, what about you? Are you hurt?
I'm fine.
You're so nice, Sasaki-san.
Huh? How do you know my name?
You're Sasaki Atsuko-san, right?
We're in the same class.
Oh...
I haven't learned the names
or faces of anyone in our class yet.
I'm sorry.
Really?
Then, I'll introduce myself now.
My name is—
She gave me a new world.
Every day was exciting and fun.
The days I had spent reading books alone
and never talking to anyone
didn't seem real anymore.
Acchan... I'm done for.
The rest is up to you.
What are you talking about?
It hasn't even been ten minutes yet.
You want to miss out on getting
into high school this year?
But I'm just so sleepy...
This reference book must have a curse
on it that makes people sleepy!
Okay, if you pass the exam,
I'll let you play my most
prized otome game all you want.
Really?! Thanks, Acchan!
I'll pass the exam to get
into high school, whatever it takes!
A
PASSING EXAMINEES
What now? Want to stop by my place?
I'm gonna head home for today.
I want to conquer the black-hearted,
sadistic prince by tonight.
You've really gotten into Fortune Lover, huh?
Okay, good luck.
Thanks! See you tomorrow!
I took for granted that those
days would last forever...
but they ended so suddenly.
She was involved in a traffic
accident on the way to school.
She'll never come back.
A
Acchan, I can't conquer the
black-hearted, sadistic prince!
This was her last message to me?
A
Acchan, I can't conquer the
black-hearted, sadistic prince!
From now on,
I'll have to live my life without her.
I'll carry on in the new world
that she gave me.
So if I have a chance
to be reborn when my life ends,
I want to be friends with her again.
Why am I...
Heave-ho...
and here we go!
Catarina-sama!
Morning, Sophia. Is something wrong?
I had a very sad dream,
and suddenly, I wanted to see you.
A dream?
Yes. It was a very, very sad dream.
I don't remember what
happened in it very clearly,
but I think it was something
that happened long ago.
Long ago?
I don't mean when I was a child.
Much, much longer ago than that...
This all sounds very strange, doesn't it?
No, it doesn't.
Bad dreams happen sometimes
when you're nervous.
Nervous?
We have exams starting today, right?
I'm sure you had a sad dream
because you're nervous about that.
But don't worry! I'm just as nervous as you!
Let's both do our best on the exams!
Okay.
I hate exams!
I just want to play all the time!
How long are you going to act
as if it's still summer vacation?
If we don't pass the exam,
we won't advance to the next grade.
But whether or not we get to
the next grade isn't what's important.
It's whether or not we get the doom ending!
Maria doesn't seem to be in love
with anyone at the moment.
She didn't have any summer flings, either!
We should continue our observation
of developments in Maria's love life.
But right now, we need to focus on the exam.
If we don't advance to the next grade...
Catarina!
How could you fail to advance
to the next grade?!
We'll get the doom ending
when our own mother kills us!
L-Let's focus on the exam.
No objections!
Your practical exam will consist
of exploring these ancient ruins.
Deep in these ruins, where it's said
that a great mage once lived,
there is a stone inhabited by magical power.
The team that brings it
back here will pass the exam.
It's a bit like a treasure hunt, isn't it?
Yeah. Sounds like fun!
Everyone, do not take this task lightly.
The ruins are as complex
as a maze on the inside.
In addition, there are various
traps set at every turn.
Traps?
I heard that the great mage set traps
to protect his magic tools from thieves.
Those traps still deter invaders to this day.
And they're tossing students
into a place like that?
These teachers and second-years
are here to serve as aides in the exam,
but still, you must not get careless.
Demonstrate your command of your
own magic and everything you've learned
to make your way
into the depths of the ruins.
Now, each team may proceed
to their chosen entrance.
Yes, sir.
You two are on the same
team as Alan-sama, right?
Yes.
I'm sad that you and I will be
separated, but I'll do my best!
I'm worried about you, for many reasons.
Be careful.
I will!
Let's do our best with our team, too.
Right!
Catarina...
Don't leave my side once we're
inside the ruins, all right?
You can count on me to look after my sister.
You really do follow us everywhere,
don't you, Keith?
It was the teachers who chose
the teams, Geordo-sama.
You may follow us, but that's all.
Did you say something?
She hardly even has any magic.
Such jokes won't work with me.
Must be nice to have so many
people around to help her out.
She even has princes helping her. It's not fair!
I see you're all together.
As you've heard, this exam is very dangerous.
Be careful.
And good luck.
It looks like the setting for a novel.
Yeah. It's so dark and spooky.
If you're scared, do you want me
to hold your hand, Sister?
As her fiancé, it's my job to escort her, Keith.
As her family, it's my job to protect her, Geordo-sama.
Huh?
I wonder what this is...
What happened?!
Sister!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Try not to touch anything!
What's that?
We won't be able to get past that ice.
But there's no other way.
We'll just have to break through it.
I see now.
This is a test to see
whether or not we can get through.
Everyone, stay back. This will be dangerous.
That's amazing, Geordo-sama!
Look!
Let's hurry through it.
Right!
It's so dark... I hope
Catarina-sama is doing all right.
She'll be fine. Geordo's with her.
That's exactly what I'm worried about.
Mary-sama, Alan-sama, what's that?
It's the stone inhabited by magical power!
This means we'll pass the exam, right?
Wait!
Don't tell me this is...
Run, both of you!
Are you all right?
Yes...
I can't believe I fell for that trap.
How careless of me.
Still, this exam is much more
dangerous than I expected.
Which way should we go?
Oh, there's something written here.
It's an ancient script.
I can't read it at all!
We've been learning ancient script in class, Sister.
Some of the characters have faded, though.
"You who wander within the labyrinth,
if you go east..."
I can't read the next part.
I know what it is!
"If you go east,
you will only march in place.
If you go west, you will struggle
to follow a strenuous path.
Only the adventurer may
proceed beyond the light."
This is a verse from a poem.
I'm amazed you knew that, Sophia!
I read it once before.
What could it mean, though?
I guess it means we should go west,
even if the path is strenuous.
I agree.
Going east may lead to a dead end.
Then we need to go that way!
You always start with the dead
ends in a dungeon! It's a rule!
There could be treasure chests there!
What are you talking about, Sister?
Let's go.
Huh? Wait...
It's not a dead end, but we can't go any farther.
We just need to swim across!
Something's in there!
What do we do?!
Leave this one to me, Sister!
That was rather breathtaking.
Yes, incredible!
Thanks, Keith!
All right, let's go.
I wish I could be useful to them, too...
Everyone, look out!
Come forth, Earth Bump!
Now we can get past it with no problem.
Well done, Catarina-sama!
Yes, you've saved the day.
Great job, Sister.
I'm glad my Earth Bump came in handy!
Huh?
Geordo-sama!
Stay back, Sister!
Is everyone all right?
Catarina?
Sister, where are you?!
Ow...
Where am I?
What do I do now?
I got separated from the others!
Geordo-sama!
Keith!
Sophia!
Where are they?
I never expected her to get lost!
Who would've thought
she'd trigger a doom flag
in a way that had nothing to do
with the game's plot?!
Well, our only choice is to keep moving!
Let's keep looking for a way out!
We don't want to waste
energy running around blindly.
Let's wait for help to arrive.
What are you doing?
Looking for food!
We'll last longer if we have food, right?
Oh! Found some!
Ugh!
I don't think it's
a good idea to eat that...
Isn't there anything else?
Oh, I found more!
This'll hold me for a while.
There's no way I'm going to die here!
Is someone there?
Wait!
Brother!
Sophia? Did something happen?
We've lost Catarina-sama!
She disappeared while we
were preoccupied with a trap.
Master Nicol, have you seen my sister?
No, she hasn't been this way.
What is it? Did something happen?
Everyone...
Catarina-sama is lost?!
Where could she have gone?
I hope she didn't get caught in a trap.
That sad dream I had this morning...
Could it have been...
You okay, Sophia?
I have a bad feeling.
We have to find Catarina-sama!
A bad feeling?
Where are you?
Catarina-sama!
That's it! Her voice!
I'm going to pick up Catarina's voice.
Pick up her voice? How?
With wind magic?
Exactly.
I can pick up people's voices
with my wind magic.
It should tell us which direction she's in.
Give it a try.
Right.
I'll help you!
That's weird.
I'm sure I heard footsteps.
I found more!
Mushrooms!
Mushrooms?
That was definitely Catarina-sama's voice!
What does "mushrooms" mean?
She didn't eat mushrooms, did she?
I'm just glad she's all right!
Let's go!
They're so hard to break loose.
This many should keep me alive
for a good, long time!
I wish I had some soy sauce,
but beggars can't be choosers.
Is someone there?
I refuse...
to meet my doom here!
Sophia!
Let go, Sophia!
No! I won't let go!
Never ever!
I don't ever want to lose you again!
Ouch...
Are you okay, Sophia?
Yes. What about you? Are you hurt?
I'm just fine!
Thank goodness!
Please don't ever leave
again, Catarina-sama!
Okay. I won't go anywhere.
Thank you for saving me, Sophia.
Was that whirlwind your magic?
No, it wasn't me.
Then... what was it?
Catarina!
Sister!
You're all right?
Yeah.
You all came to find me?
Thank goodness, Catarina-sama!
Sorry for worrying you.
Hey, that stone...
It's the stone inhabited by magical power!
Th-This thing?
You did it, Catarina-sama!
Now we'll pass the exam!
Where did you find it?
Um, actually...
This many should keep me alive
for a good, long time!
I was so hungry, I got
absorbed in mushroom hunting,
so I didn't even realize it was
the stone inhabited by magical power.
You never change, Sister.
Catarina remains strong and reliable,
no matter the situation she's in.
Yeah.
What was that?
Okay! We're having a mushroom party today!
You want us to eat those?
That color looks kind of poisonous...
If Catarina-sama offers me food,
I'll eat it even if it means my death!
M-Me, too!
Th-That's really not necessary!
I'm making mushroom broth!
No! Don't eat it!
What is "mushroom broth"?
kokoro ga tsukiru made moyase
My heart yearns for you so much
kantan ni clear dekiru
I thought it was easy to clear
koi wa game sou omotteta
To win at this love game
gururi madowasete hikiyosete
I'm spinning around and pulling you in
otosu shudai wo narabuke wo
Following along in my footsteps
naze kimi dakara igai
Why are you so captivating?
dono route erabeba saita nano ka
Which route will be the best choice?
kotae wa mienai
I can't find the answer
Bad End no unmei demo boku no mono ni nareba ii
Even if fate leads me to a "Bad End", it's fine
sou saa douse hametsu suru no nara kimi to
You're the one I want in my life
zettai ni zetsumei shinai aida to chikaukara
My love for you will never change
ubai saa nareru kakugo
Prepare to be conquered
mubou mi de muteki nayosashisa mudai makichirasu mae ni
You make me feel invincible, imprudent and happy at the same time
sono chisen wo hitorijime shitte miseru
I want to find out more about you
donna kodoku mo itami mo
No matter how much the pain is
kimi goto uketomeru
I will carry it for you
machi ukeru zetsubou mo nozomu tokoro
Even if despair awaits me, I'll take it on